Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage artistic personnel, 1950-2000; 9.5 linear feet (8 boxes)
  - Adale O'Brien, actress (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Connie O'Connell, actress (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Pat O'Brien, actor (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - M.C. O'Connor, actor (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Debbie Offner, actress (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Fred O'Neil, actor (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Terry O'Quinn, actor (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Eddy Ormond, actor (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Flo Ormond, actress (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Kevin O'Rourke, actor (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Theresea O'Rourke, actress (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Kurt Orwick, actress (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Julie Osburn, actress (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Paul Owen, set designer (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Sharon Ott, director (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Roger Oliner, actor (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Alexander Okuh, scenic designer (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Michael O'Hare, actor (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Terrence O'Hara, actor (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Constance Ogden, actress (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Meg Kelly and Eddy Ormond, actor and actress (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ronald Drake, actor (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Augustine Dunn, actor (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Kathryn Dowling, actress (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Marjorie Feiner, actress (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Laurie Franks, actress (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Carol Gustafson, actress (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Gene Gross, actor (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jane Groves, actress (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rosalind Harris, actress (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - David Haviland, actor (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - George Hosmer, actor (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ann Ives, actress (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Zviah Igdalsky, actress (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Laurie Kennedy, actress (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Elaine Kerr, actress (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Marketa Kimbrell, actress (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - John Kuhner, actor (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Julie Kurnitz, actress (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Rosemary Knower, actress (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Lee Lawson, actress (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Tom Lehrer, actor (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Barbara Lester, actress (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Michael Levin, actor (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Michael Lewis, actor (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Mark Linn-Baker, actor (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Judith Long, actress (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Yuri Lyubimov, director (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Joe Morton, actor (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Peter Maclean, actor (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Walt MacPherson, actor (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Robert Pastene, ??? (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Michael Petro, actor (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Rick Podell, actor (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Rick Pollack, ??? (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Bruce Hopkins, actor (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Hy Kalus, actor (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - unknown (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - unknown (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - unknown (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - misc. unkown (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - misc. unknown (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Richard Russell Ramos, actor (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ed Rompola, actor (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Paul Rudd, actor (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Ken Ruta, actor (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Alfred Ryder, actor (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jack Ryland, actor (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - William Stewart, actor (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ira Siff, actor (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - April Shawhan, actress (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Phyllis Sommerville, actress (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Maureen sadusk, actress (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Rick Sabatini, actor (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Manu Tupou, actor (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Kristie Tucker, actress (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - misc. photos (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Arena Stage actor biographical information and photographs, 1950-1960s; 1.5 linear feet (3 boxes)
  Collection includes actor photographs and short biographies.
  - Photograph of a man, unidentified (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Actor biographies A-C, 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Actors biographies, A-C, 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Actors biographies A-C, 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Actors biographies D-F, 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Actor biographies D-F, 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Actor biographies, G-L (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Actor biographies, F-H (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Actor biographies, I-L (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Includes bio and photo for James Earl Jones.
  - Actor biographies, M (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Actor biographies N-O (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Actor biographies, P-R (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Actor biographies, S-Z (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Women actor biographies, A-C (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Women actor biographies, D-F (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Women actor biographies, G-K (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Women actor biographies, K-M (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Women actor biographies N - R (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Women actor biographies S - Z (Box 3, Folder 6)